blend.com 2019-12-21

# Privacy Policy - Blend

_Effective date: September 6, 2016_

This Privacy Statement applies to www.blendlabs.com, which is owned and operated by Blend Labs, Inc. (“Blend” or “Company”). This Privacy Statement describes how Blend collects and uses the personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) acquired through your use of the Blend website (“Services”). It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of, your access to, and how to update and correct your Personal Information.

By using or accessing the Services in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Statement, and you hereby consent to our collecting, using, and sharing your information in the following ways.

## Collection and use of Personal Information

We collect Personal Information, such as your name, email address, and phone number, so we can send you requested product or service information, respond to your questions and concerns, and make you aware of product or service offerings.

## Sharing of Personal Information

We will share your Personal Information with third parties as described in this Privacy Statement. We may also disclose your Personal Information to any third party with your prior consent.

### PROVIDING THE SERVICES

Blend may transfer Personal Information to companies that help us provide our Services. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this Privacy Statement.

### COMPLIANCE WITH LEGAL OBLIGATIONS

We may also disclose your Personal Information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, bankruptcy proceedings, or similar legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

### ANALYSIS OF ANONYMIZED DATA

We may anonymize your Personal Information so that you are not individually identified, and provide that information to our partners. We may also provide aggregate usage information to our partners, who may use such information to understand how often and in what ways people use the Services, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal online experience. However, we never disclose aggregate usage information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally, as an individual. We may use third-party analytics services, such as Mixpanel, grow our business, improve and develop our Services, monitor and analyze use of our Services, aid our technical administration, increase the functionality and user-friendliness of our Services, and verify that users have provided the authorization we need to process user requests. These analytics services may collect and retain anonymized information about you.

You can opt-out of Mixpanel’s automatic retention of data collected while using the Services by visiting <https://mixpanel.com/optout/>. If you get a new computer, install a new browser, or erase or otherwise alter your browser’s cookie file (including upgrading certain browsers), you may clear the Mixpanel opt-out cookie, and you will need to re-visit the opt-out page. Note that Mixpanel’s opt-out cookies will not stop us from sending other data about you from our servers to Mixpanel, nor will it prevent any other data collection methods. To learn more about the Privacy Policy of Mixpanel, visit <https://mixpanel.com/privacy/>.

## Opt-out preferences

We may communicate with you if you’ve provided us the means to do so. For example, if you’ve given us your email address, we may you about your use of our Services. Also, we may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. This confirmation helps us make our communications with you more interesting and improve our Services. If you do not want to receive communications from us, please indicate your preference by contacting [support@blendlabs.com](mailto:support@blendlabs.com).

## User access and choice

If you wish to request access or deletion of your Personal Information, please contact us at [support@blendlabs.com](mailto:support@blendlabs.com). We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

We will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you the Services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. If you have any questions about the security of your Personal Information, you can contact us at [support@blendlabs.com](mailto:support@blendlabs.com).

## Tracking technologies

We and our partners use technologies such as cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track user movements around the website, and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. Your browser may offer you a “Do Not Track” option, which allows you to signal to operators of websites and web applications and services (including behavioral advertising services) that you do not wish such operators to track certain of your online activities over time and/or across different websites. The Services do not support Do Not Track requests at this time, which means that we collect information about your online activity both while you are using and after you leave the Services. We partner with a third party either to display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third-party partner may use cookies or similar technologies to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising, click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (“IP”) addresses, browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve the Services, or to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality.

## Links to other sites

Our website includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Blend. If you submit Personal Information to any of those websites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit.

Our website may include social media features, such as the Facebook or Twitter button or interactive mini-programs that run on our website. These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it.

## Changes to this Privacy Statement

We may update this Privacy Statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### CONTACT INFORMATION

Blend Labs, Inc.  
415 Kearny Street  
San Francisco, CA 94108  
(650) 550-4810
